The world of the dead and the world of the living... are about to collide
Soul Survivors is a horror, mystery, thriller
film directed by Stephen Carpenter.
A college freshman involved in a fatal car crash discovers she may not have survived after
all when she becomes caught between the worlds of the living and the dead.
Cassie, played by Melissa Sagemiller.
Matt, played by Wes Bentley.
Sean, played by Casey Affleck.
Annabel, played by Eliza Dushku.
Raven, played by Angela Featherstone.
Jude, played by Luke Wilson.
Soul Survivors is a 2001 psychological thriller film directed by Stephen Carpenter and starring Melissa Sagemiller as college student
Cassie, whose boyfriend Sean (Casey Affleck) dies in a car accident that results from her driving after a night of partying.
The accident leaves Cassie wracked with guilt and emotionally vulnerable to the point that she begins hallucinating strange visions and waking-dreams, even as Cassie's
friends Annabel (Eliza Dushku) and Matt (Wes Bentley), as well as a local priest, Father Jude (Luke Wilson), attempt to assist her in coping with the loss.
The film explores themes of hallucination, car crash, death, sole survivor.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.